errorfix.com 2013-08-28

# Welcome to ErrorFix - Scan, Repair & Speed Your PC

PC Utility Inc., (representative of ErrorFix, ErrorFix.com and hereafter represented as "we", "us", or "our") is committed to the privacy of our users. All personally identifying information provided to us on any of our Internet Services is hereto considered private. This Policy details how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to any of ErrorFix.com Internet properties.

**Private Information & the Web**  
When you agree to purchase ErrorFix or other PC Utilities Inc software, we may collect personally identifying information for the purpose of enacting a transaction. This information includes your name, your address, and your email address. When and if we use a payment processing merchant, we take steps to ensure that the processing merchant has strict privacy criteria are in place. We do not sell or share your personally identifiable information to third parties, except with your express consent by opting in (with a right to opt out if you change your mind) or when we have a good faith belief that it is required by law, such as in response to a subpoena or other order of a court or governmental agency.

We do not (knowingly) collect or use any personally identifying information from a person who is a minor without first obtaining verifiable parental consent for the collection or use of such information, except for the limited purposes of responding to a request from the minor (such information not being maintained in retrievable form) or a request for the name of a parent when made for the sole purpose of obtaining consent for the collection of information about the minor. If we do collect personally identifiable information about a minor, a parent is permitted to obtain any data his/her child has provided to us and may request that we delete such data and/or not collect further data by contacting us at [support@ErrorFix.com](mailto:support@ErrorFix.com).

**Web Security**  
Any and all personal information we collect about you in regards to a transaction is stored in limited access servers. We maintain these safeguards to protect the security of our servers and the data and privacy of our customers. We keep personally identifiable information only as long as is necessary to fully complete a transaction, deter fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your user account with us. We take appropriate measures to assure the reliability of our data security systems and the information that they contain. We take reasonable precautions to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personally identifiable information and to protect it from loss, misuse or alteration. In the event that we do, with your consent, share your personally identifiable information with a third party, we will take reasonable steps to assure that the third party is aware of these security practices and that the third party will also take reasonable precautions to protect any transferred information.

**Use of Cookies** ErrorFix.com uses cookies to assign non-unique, non-identifiable information to machines that access our services. PC Utilities Inc, defines a cookie as a string of data that is automatically stored on your (the customer's) computer upon access to our services. The information provided by the cookie allows us to deliver faster services to you, to other customers, and/or to our affiliates. The cookie also aids us in the prevention of denial of service (DoS) attacks on our systems; the detection and prevention of fraudulent transactions; and assistance in awarding proper sales credit to our online partners. Hereto, the cookies used by Errorfix.com are never used as a way of extended customer tracking nor are they ever distributed to any party outside of PC Utilites Inc.

All ErrorFix.com cookies are:  

  1. temporary, having a limited duration
  2. small, less than 5KB in length
  3. discreet, only visible to ErrorFix.com
  4. non-identifying, devoid of personally identifiable information
  5. non-unique, being maintained to track our affiliates so as to ensure proper payments for their sales.

**What Information Does ErrorFix Collect?**  
Neither ErrorFix.com nor ErrorFix Software collects any personally identifying information from your computer. As an aspect of is purpose, Errorfix creats logs of its actions and items detected in the form of simple, text-based log files. These logs are stored on your harddrive and are only accessible to you. They provide you with a way of viewing ErrorFix's actions and also provide tech support with a way of assessing problems. In a support situation, the tech assistant may request the view the log for troubleshooting purposes but the option to do so lies solely with you.

Neither ErrorFix.com nor ErrorFix software sends information about you or your computer to anyone.

**How Does ErrorFix Use the Information it Collects?**  
We may implement private data in the following ways only:  

  * To enable us to process, verify and validate purchases.
  * To register you as a customer of ErrorFix and to open and/or maintain a support account for you. Such an account is created to provide support services for our customers.
  * To obtain customer feedback, help enhance product features or provide additional products and services.
  * To distribute email notifications about existing, new, or enhanced products or services. These emails constitute information on special offers, or attempts to contact you as a measure to confirm or verify the accuracy of information provided to us. **_Please note, that PC Utilities Inc. adheres to a strict policy of customer privacy in that we will never sell and/or distribute a customer's email address to a third party_**.

We reserve the right to disclose and use any personally identifying information in special circumstances wherein it is necessary to enforce service agreements or terms of use. For example, we may disclose private data to protect our intellectual property rights. Additionally, we may disclose or use personal information when we believe, in good faith, that the law may require us to do so. 

**ErrorFix Updates**  
Once installed, your copy of ErrorFix will routinely check in with our server to receive software updates. These updates constitute information that ErrorFix uses to detect and remove new errors. The update process can be modified through Settings dialog. By default, the update service is set to notify you when an update is available but to only download said update when you grant express permission.

**How to Opt Out of Receiving E-mail Communications From Us**  
We may periodically send our customers unsolicited e-mails advertising or promoting our commercial products and services. If you wish to opt out of receiving such future commercial e-mail communications from us, you may follow the unsubscribe link contained in the e-mail you receive or as directed at www.errorfix.com/unsubscribe_email.php. Unsubscribing means that you will receive no future unsolicited advertising or promotions e-mail communications from us. You will, however, continue to receive e-mail communications relating to transactions that you have already agreed to or products or services that you have already purchased. If you do not wish to receive even these e-mail communications, please contact us at [support@ErrorFix.com](mailto:support@ErrorFix.com).

**Policy Modification**  
From time to time, we may change parts of this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted here promptly, so please check back periodically.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, feel free to contact us at [support@ErrorFix.com](mailto:support@ErrorFix.com).
